Guide to the Martha Wilson Papers, 1950-2019 (bulk 1964-2006) MSS.175
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Correspondence, 1964-2013; 172383
  - Subseries A: General Correspondence, 190087
    - Rothenberg, Ellen, 1983; 207145 (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Rothenberg, Erika, 1986-1991, undated; 207146 (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - Rousseve, David, 1988; 207147 (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - Rowley, Roger, 2002; 207148 (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - Roy [Colnek], 2002-2003, undated; 207218 (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - Rozsa, John and Loretta, 1980-2001, undated; 207219 (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - Rozsa, Loretta, 1965-2003, undated; 207220 (Box 17, Folder 58)
    - Rubin, Chandra, undated; 207221 (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - Rubin, Dan, 1981-1986, undated; 207222 (Box 17, Folder 60)
    - Rubin, Deborah, 1982-1990; 207223 (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - Rubin, Dorothy, 1987-2009, undated; 207224 (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - Rubin, Jason, 1977-2001; 207225 (Box 17, Folder 63)
    - Rubin, Samuel (also contains materials addressed to Fernando), 1982; 207226 (Box 17, Folder 64)
    - Rubin, Gail and Conrad Greber and JP and David, 1978-2004, undated; 207227 (Box 17, Folder 65)
    - Rubinstein, David/Adelphi U, 1986; 207228 (Box 17, Folder 66)
    - [Rudin], Alice, 1987. undated; 207229 (Box 17, Folder 67)
    - Rudy, Steven, 1986; 207230 (Box 17, Folder 68)
    - Ruello, Catherine (also contains material from Wilson), 1993; 207231 (Box 17, Folder 69)
    - Rumm, Ellen, 1976-1992, undated; 207232 (Box 17, Folder 70)
    - Rumm, Ellen and Ian Goldberg, 1987-1988; 207233 (Box 17, Folder 71)
    - Ruocco, Roberta/ JP Morgan, 1993; 207234 (Box 17, Folder 72)
    - Mr. Rush, undated; 207235 (Box 17, Folder 73)
    - Ruskin, Donna, 1989; 207458 (Box 17, Folder 74)
    - Russell, Mark/ PS 122, 1985-2006; 207459 (Box 17, Folder 75)
    - Russell, Susan, undated; 207460 (Box 17, Folder 76)
    - Rutgers/John Bettenbender/Mark Berger, 1979-1990; 207461 (Box 17, Folder 77)
    - Rutgers/ The Feminist Art Project/ Tiffany Calvert, 2006; 207462 (Box 17, Folder 78)
    - Rutgers Center for Innocative Print and Paper/ Chris Erickson/ Lynne Allen, 2005; 207463 (Box 17, Folder 79)
    - Ruth and Michael, 2007, undated; 207464 (Box 17, Folder 80)
    - Rutkovsky, Paul, 1991; 207465 (Box 17, Folder 81)
    - Rutzky, Ivy, 1978; 207466 (Box 17, Folder 82)
    - Ryan and Marital, undated; 207467 (Box 17, Folder 83)
    - Ryan and Tiffany, 2008; 207468 (Box 17, Folder 84)
    - Ryniker, Jeanne, 1964; 207469 (Box 17, Folder 85)
    - Ryther Child Center/ Lillian Johnson, 1967; 207470 (Box 17, Folder 86)
    - S, 1983-1984; 207471 (Box 17, Folder 87)
    - S. Valentin, 1980; 207472 (Box 17, Folder 88)
    - Saad, Aleya/ Arttable, 1995; 207473 (Box 17, Folder 89)
    - Saar, Alison and Tom, 1990-2001; 207474 (Box 17, Folder 90)
    - Sabbatino/Mary/Arttable, 1995-2004; 207475 (Box 17, Folder 91)
    - Sacerío, Alex and Paula, 2005; 207476 (Box 17, Folder 92)
    - Sackoff, Judith, 2005; 207477 (Box 17, Folder 93)
    - [Sadbuek], Ann, 2003; 207478 (Box 17, Folder 94)
    - Sadeg, Narmine, 1993-1994; 207479 (Box 17, Folder 95)
    - Salley Mae, undated; 207480 (Box 17, Folder 96)
    - Salpeter, Ellen/ Thread waxing Space, 1996; 207481 (Box 17, Folder 97)
    - Samaras, Isabel, 1995-2002; 207482 (Box 17, Folder 98)
    - Samson, LIsa/ Betz, Samson, Shah, 2001-2007; 207483 (Box 17, Folder 99)
    - Samuel, Carol, 1964; 207484 (Box 17, Folder 100)
    - Sanborn, Keith, undated; 207485 (Box 17, Folder 101)
    - Sanchez, Alba, 1997-1998; 207486 (Box 17, Folder 102)
    - Sandberg, Eric, undated; 207487 (Box 17, Folder 103)
    - Sandi and Bob, undated; 207488 (Box 17, Folder 104)
    - Sandrow, Hope, 1992; 207489 (Box 17, Folder 105)
    - Sandy, 1977; 207490 (Box 17, Folder 106)
    - Sanner, James, 1967-1969; 207491 (Box 17, Folder 107)
    - Letter from Callie Wilson to James Sanner, 1968; 207492 (Box 17, Folder 108)
    - The Sangers, undated; 207493 (Box 17, Folder 109)
    - Sansone, Tom, 1979, undated; 207494 (Box 17, Folder 110)
    - Sant, Toni, 2000-2004; 207495 (Box 17, Folder 111)
    - Santa Fe Art Institute/ Sarah Spengler/Eileen Torpey, 2005, undated; 207496 (Box 17, Folder 112)
    - Sappol, Nell, 1993; 207497 (Box 17, Folder 113)
    - Sara, undated; 207498 (Box 17, Folder 114)
    - Sarah, 2002; 207499 (Box 17, Folder 115)
    - Sarah [Holland], 1983-1984, undated; 207500 (Box 17, Folder 116)
    - Satin, Claire Jeanine, date illegible; 207501 (Box 17, Folder 117)
    - Savitt, Jane, 1976; 207502 (Box 17, Folder 118)
    - Scarlatos, Elizabeth, 1984-1987; 207503 (Box 17, Folder 119)
    - Scattergood School, 1968; 207504 (Box 17, Folder 120)
    - Schacter, David/ Harry Abrams Inc., 1975; 207505 (Box 17, Folder 121)
    - Schaller, Rhonda, 207506 (Box 17, Folder 122)
    - Schechner, Richard, 1998-2001; 207507 (Box 17, Folder 123)
    - Schel, 1998; 207508 (Box 17, Folder 124)
    - Scheuer, Betsey, 1968; 207509 (Box 17, Folder 125)
    - Scheib, Jay, undated; 207510 (Box 17, Folder 126)
    - Schiff, Artie/ Hyp-no-habit, 1984; 207511 (Box 17, Folder 127)
    - Schiffman, Carl and Jacquelyn, 1995-2003; 207512 (Box 17, Folder 128)
    - Schiller/Vitale, 2006; 207610 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Schlesinger, Christina, 1997-1998, undated; 207611 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Schneemann, Carolee, 1990-1997, undated; 207612 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Schobel, John/ The New York Academy of Art, 1996; 207613 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Schoffel, Jospeh, 1976; 207614 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - The School of the Art Institute of Chicago/ Valier Cassel, 1998; 207630 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - School of Visual Arts/ Francis Mclaughlin-Gill, 1979; 207631 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Schor, Mira, 1976-1980; 207632 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Schor, Mira and Susan Bee, 1978-1993; 207633 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Schreibman, Vida, 1994-1995; 207634 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Schuster, Sarah/ Maine College of Art, 2001-2002; 207635 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Shram, Rosalyn, 1993; 207636 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Schwalb, Susan, 1976-1977; 207637 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Schwartz, Ellen and Fred Harris, 1991; 207638 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Schwartz, Gary, 1998; 207666 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Schwartzman, Amy, 1999; 207667 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Schwedder, Bill, undated; 207668 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Scott, 1979; 207669 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Scott, Dread, 1998-2007, undated; 207670 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Screen Actors Guild, 1995; 207671 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Seagull, Sara, undated; 207672 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Sean, 207673 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Sebastian, undated; 207674 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Segal, Mark, 2007; 207675 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Seigel, Judy, 1984; 207676 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Sell, Michael, 1992; 207677 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Semah, Joseph, 1984; 207678 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Semmel, Joan, 1998-2000; 207679 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Senft, Terri/ NYU, ITP, 2005; 207680 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Seorza, Christina, 2001; 207687 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Serebrennikov, Nina/Davidson College, 1999; 207688 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Sexton, Lucy, 1995-1996; 207689 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - SF Camera Work/Karla Milosevich and Dan Orendorff, 2007; 207690 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Share, Susan, 1992-1998; 207691 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Sharifi, Frishta, 2007; 207692 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Sharon, 1976; 207693 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Sharon F., undated; 207960 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Sharon, Miriam, 1993; 207961 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Sharon, Skutá and Thedóra, undated; 207962 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Sharp, Willoughby and Pamela Smith, 1990-2005; 207963 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Shapiro, Leo, 1992; 207964 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Shapiro, Miriam, 1990; 207965 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Shaw. Angel, 2001; 207966 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Shaw, Joyce Cutler, 1976-2008; 207967 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Shaw, Karen, 1976-2008; 207968 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Sheehan, Maura, undated; 207969 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Sheer, Doug, 2006; 207970 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Shel, 1977; 207971 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Shelly, 1985; 207972 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Sheppard, Charles, 2006; 207977 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Sherk, Bonnie, 2001; 207973 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Sherman, Karen, 2001-2003; 207974 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Sherman, Lucy Wilson, 1972-2000; 207975 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Sherman, Lucie, Artie, and Becky, 1965; 207976 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Sherman, Stuart, 1977; 207978 (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Shestack, Mel, 1986; 207979 (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Shimoda, Seiji / NIPAF '96, 1991-1998; Undated; 207980 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Shinohara, Ushio, 1987; 207981 (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - Shoger, Jan, 1996; 207982 (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - Sholette, Greg, 1999; 207983 (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - Shattenkirk, Dena and Coates, Peter Taylor, 2000; Undated; 207984 (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - Shultz, Ellen, 1975; 207985 (Box 18, Folder 62)
    - Siah and Barbara, Undated; 207986 (Box 18, Folder 63)
    - Sibio, Linda Carmella, 2003-2009; Undated; 207987 (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - Siegel and Gale, 1985; 207988 (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - Siena, Iris Rose and James, 1988; 207989 (Box 18, Folder 66)
    - Sifuentes, Roberto, 2001; 207990 (Box 18, Folder 67)
    - Sikoryak, Bob and Krista Willberg, 2001-2004; 207991 (Box 18, Folder 68)
    - Silberstein-Storfer, Muriel, 1984-1991; 207992 (Box 18, Folder 69)
    - Silveira, Regina, 1994; Undated; 207993 (Box 18, Folder 70)
    - Silver, Doni, 1978; Undated; 207994 (Box 18, Folder 71)
    - Silver, Sheldon, 2005; 207995 (Box 18, Folder 72)
    - Silverman, Leonard B. / D.V.M., 1986; 207996 (Box 18, Folder 73)
    - Silvia, Pet(e), 1998; 207997 (Box 18, Folder 74)
    - Silvio, Undated; 207998 (Box 18, Folder 75)
    - Simonian, Judith, 1990; 207999 (Box 18, Folder 76)
    - Sims, Lowery, 1984; 208000 (Box 18, Folder 77)
    - Sinclair, Sheila, 1983; 208001 (Box 18, Folder 78)
    - Sischy, Ingrid, 1978-2002; 208002 (Box 18, Folder 79)
    - Skadden, Arps, Slate, Meagher, and Flom, 1977; 208003 (Box 18, Folder 80)
    - Skinner, Mike, 1992-1994; 208004 (Box 18, Folder 81)
    - Slater, Kathy, 1977; 208005 (Box 18, Folder 82)
    - Slifka, Rose, 1981; 208006 (Box 18, Folder 83)
    - Sloan, Jennifer, 1994; 208007 (Box 18, Folder 84)
    - Sloan, Judith, 1993; 208008 (Box 18, Folder 85)
    - Slonge, Carol, 1977; 208009 (Box 18, Folder 86)
    - Smith, Arthur and Melva, 1983-1997; 208010 (Box 18, Folder 87)
    - Smith, Barbara, 1987-1990; 208011 (Box 18, Folder 88)
    - Smith, Barry, 2006-2007; 208012 (Box 18, Folder 89)
    - Smith, Champe, 2008; 208013 (Box 18, Folder 90)
    - Smith, Doug and Pat, 1985-2008; Undated; 208014 (Box 18, Folder 91)
    - Smith, Douglas and Florence, 1979-2002; Undated; 208015 (Box 18, Folder 92)
    - Smith, Esther, 1991-2008; Undated; 208016 (Box 18, Folder 93)
    - Smith, Ivins and Esther, 1981; 208017 (Box 18, Folder 94)
    - Smith, Florence (Aunt Flo), 1976-2005; Undated; 208018 (Box 18, Folder 95)
    - Smith, Jim, 1995; 208019 (Box 18, Folder 96)
    - Smith, Melva, 1988-2001; Undated; 208020 (Box 18, Folder 97)
    - Smith, Michael (includes material from Martha Wilson), 1976-1981; Undated; 208021 (Box 18, Folder 98)
    - Smith, Michael / Baby IKKE, Undated; 208022 (Box 18, Folder 99)
    - Smith (multiples) for Woodman Reunion, 2001-2003; 208023 (Box 18, Folder 100)
    - Snitzer, Jim, 1979; 208024 (Box 18, Folder 101)
    - Snyder, Mary / NSCAD, 1995; 208025 (Box 18, Folder 102)
    - Sol and Carol, illegible; 208026 (Box 18, Folder 103)
    - Sollins, Susan, 1985; 208027 (Box 18, Folder 104)
    - Solomon, Elke, 1990-1997; 208028 (Box 18, Folder 105)
    - Solomon, Holly, Undated; 208029 (Box 18, Folder 106)
    - Sondheim, Alan, 1974-2005; Undated; 208030 (Box 18, Folder 107)
    - Sonnabend, Jennifer, Undated; 208031 (Box 18, Folder 108)
    - Sophia, 2005; 208032 (Box 18, Folder 109)
    - Sorel, Katherine, 2002; 208033 (Box 18, Folder 110)
    - Sorenson, Karen, 2003-2004; 208034 (Box 18, Folder 111)
    - Souchuk, Perry, 1989-1992; 208035 (Box 18, Folder 112)
    - Southern, Hugh / NEA, 1984; 208036 (Box 18, Folder 113)
    - Spear, Duston, 1994-2004; 208037 (Box 18, Folder 114)
    - Speagle, Trey, 1986; 208038 (Box 18, Folder 115)
    - Spencer, Thomas / Friar's Lantern, 1998; 208039 (Box 18, Folder 116)
    - Spero, Nancy, 1982-2002; 208040 (Box 18, Folder 117)
    - Spiegel, Emily and Jerry, 1987; 208041 (Box 18, Folder 118)
    - Spiegel-Sorel, Valerie, 1984; 208042 (Box 18, Folder 119)
    - Spiker, David, 1989-1991; 208043 (Box 18, Folder 120)
    - [Spiller, Harley] 1 of 2, various; 208044 (Box 18, Folder 121)
    - [Spiller, Harley] 2 of 2, Various; 208045 (Box 18, Folder 122)
    - Spiller, Harley and Kevin, Undated; 208046 (Box 18, Folder 123)
    - Split Britches, 2000; 208047 (Box 18, Folder 124)
    - Sprinkle, Annie, 1991-2005; Undated; 208048 (Box 18, Folder 125)
    - Spivy, Jock, 1999; 208049 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Stackhouse, Robert M., 1976; 208050 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Stacy, 2000; 208051 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Stanffacher, Cary, 1986; 208052 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Stanley, [Dan], 1977; 208053 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - stART, 2003; 208054 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Stave, Pari, 1989; 208055 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Steckel, Anita, 2006-2008; 208056 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Stedman, Susan, 2008; 208057 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Stein, Bob, 2001; 208058 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Stein, Donna and Korn, Henry, 1986-1987; 208059 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Stein, Julie, 2001; Undated; 208060 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Stein, Lewis, 1975; 208061 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Steinbach, Haim, 1982; 208062 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Steinbach, Leonard, 1998-2006; 208063 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Stelarc, Undated; 208064 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Stephanie, 1980-1983; 208065 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Stephen, Kyle - for Lynn Hershman Leeson, 2006; 208066 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Steve, 1995; 208067 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Steve, Regina, and Tom, 1978; 208068 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Stevens, May, 1990-1994; 208069 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Stiles, Kristine, 1995-1998; 208070 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Stina and Adrienne, 2002; 208071 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Stora, DeWitt, 1967; 208072 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Storr, Rob, 1998; 208073 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Story Corps Alumni, 2007; 208074 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Streb, Elizabeth, 1994-1995; 208075 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Street, Mark, 2002; 208076 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Streitfeld, Lisa Paul, 2008; 208077 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Stringer, Elizabeth, 1992; 208078 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Stuart, 1990; 208079 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Stuart, Michelle, 1999; 208080 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Subramaniam, Radhika / Off the Record, 2006; 208081 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Sue and Adam, Undated; 208082 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Sukop, Sylvia / Women's Caucus for Art, 1994; 208083 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Sullivan, Anna, 1988-2001; Undated; 208084 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Sullivan, Cara, 2001-2004; 208085 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Sullivan, Catherine, 2001; 208086 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Summers, Elaine, Undated; 208087 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Sun, Carol, 1990-1998; 208088 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Sun, Nancy, Undated; 208089 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Suncoast Seabird Sanctuary, 1987; 208090 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - SUNY New Paltz / Patricia Phillips, 2006; 208091 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Suppa, Vito, 2002; 208092 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Surls, James, 1981; 208093 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Susan, 1967; 208094 (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Susan, 1987-2000; Undated; 208095 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - Susan [Louise], 1967; 208096 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Sutcliffe, J., 1985; 208097 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Sutton, Judy, 1987-1992; Undated; 208098 (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - Sutton, Judy and Spiker, David, 1987-1988; Undated; 208099 (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - Swartz, Gary, 1984; 208100 (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - Sweeny, Ann, 1988; 208101 (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - Sweeny, Bill, 1991; 208102 (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - Swift, Betsey, 1965; 208103 (Box 19, Folder 55)
    - Sylvia Rivera Law Project, 2002-2005; 208104 (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - T., undated; 208291 (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - Anne T., 1983; 208292 (Box 19, Folder 58)
    - T., Tom, undated; 208293 (Box 19, Folder 59)
    - [T A S], 1977; 208294 (Box 19, Folder 60)
    - Tajiri, Rea, 1991; 208295 (Box 19, Folder 61)
    - Talarico, Lita/ SVA, 2000; 208296 (Box 19, Folder 62)
    - Talen, Bill, 2000; 208297 (Box 19, Folder 63)
    - Talen, Julie, 2004; 208298 (Box 19, Folder 64)
    - Taller Portobelo Artist Retreat/ Oronike Odeleye, 2006; 208299 (Box 19, Folder 65)
    - Tanenbaum, Ann, 2004; 208300 (Box 19, Folder 66)
    - Tangeman Gallery, 1991; 208301 (Box 19, Folder 67)
    - Tankel, Claire, 1984; 208302 (Box 19, Folder 68)
    - Tannenbaum, Barbara, 1978; 208303 (Box 19, Folder 69)
    - Tannenbaum, Judith, 2007; 208304 (Box 19, Folder 70)
    - Tanselle, G. Thomas, 1990; 208305 (Box 19, Folder 71)
    - Tardes, Anne, 1981; 208306 (Box 19, Folder 72)
    - Tavenner, Patricia, 1979; 208307 (Box 19, Folder 73)
    - Taylor, Bonnie, 1987-1992; 208308 (Box 19, Folder 74)
    - Taylor and Francis, undated; 208309 (Box 19, Folder 75)
    - Taylor, Frederick and William, 1992-1994, undated; 208310 (Box 19, Folder 76)
    - Taylor, Frederick - also contains materials from Ronald Feldman and Ruth Sackner, 1989-1991; 208311 (Box 19, Folder 77)
    - Taylor, Frederick/ Skowhegan School of Painting and Sculpture, 1991; 208312 (Box 19, Folder 78)
    - Taylor, Marvin, 2007-2008, undated; 208313 (Box 19, Folder 79)
    - Taylor, Simon, 2002; 208314 (Box 19, Folder 80)
    - Taylor, Steed, 2001; 208315 (Box 19, Folder 81)
    - Ted, Carlos, Tom [Let], undated; 208316 (Box 19, Folder 82)
    - Tertelbaum, Penelope Naylor, 1985; 208317 (Box 19, Folder 83)
    - Telephone messages, undated; 208318 (Box 19, Folder 84)
    - Templeton, Fiona, 2008; 208319 (Box 19, Folder 85)
    - Tewes, Robin, 1990-2007, undated; 208320 (Box 19, Folder 87)
    - Tex, 1976; 208321 (Box 19, Folder 88)
    - Thatcher, Margaret/ Dia Art Foundation, 1982; 208322 (Box 19, Folder 89)
    - Thon, Steve, 1978-1979; 208323 (Box 19, Folder 90)
    - Theodora, Sharon and Skuta [Kulik], undated; 208324 (Box 19, Folder 91)
    - Theresa, undated; 208325 (Box 19, Folder 92)
    - Thomas, Gail, 2001; 208326 (Box 19, Folder 93)
    - Thomas, R. David, 2001; 208327 (Box 19, Folder 94)
    - Thomas, Sarah and Tim Gulden, 2001; 208328 (Box 19, Folder 95)
    - Thompson, Louise /NOW NYS, 1992; 208329 (Box 19, Folder 96)
    - Thrall, Bart, 1976; 208330 (Box 19, Folder 97)
    - Thrall, Bart, 1976-1977; 208331 (Box 19, Folder 98)
    - Thurmer, Robert/ Cleveland Performance Art Festival, 208332 (Box 19, Folder 99)
    - Tichane, Robin, 1994; 208333 (Box 19, Folder 100)
    - Tiffany, 1999, undated; 208334 (Box 19, Folder 101)
    - Tillman, Lynne, 1976-2000,undated; 208335 (Box 19, Folder 102)
    - Tim K., 1984; 208336 (Box 19, Folder 103)
    - Tina, 1993; 208337 (Box 19, Folder 104)
    - Tisdale, Daniel, 2001; 208338 (Box 19, Folder 105)
    - Tobias, Jennifer, 2007; 208339 (Box 19, Folder 106)
    - Toche, Jean, 2000-2005; 208340 (Box 19, Folder 107)
    - Tofte, Kirk and Barb and Charles and Ronni Hollander, 2008; 208341 (Box 19, Folder 108)
    - Tolentino, Julie, 2000; 208342 (Box 19, Folder 109)
    - Tom, 1975; 208343 (Box 19, Folder 110)
    - Tom, undated; 208344 (Box 19, Folder 111)
    - Tom, Jeannie, John, Mike, Ryan and Annie, 2001; 208345 (Box 19, Folder 112)
    - Tomczak, Kim / V Tape, 1995-2007; 208346 (Box 19, Folder 113)
    - Tone, Yasunao, 1987; 208347 (Box 19, Folder 114)
    - Tonelace, Carey, 1999; 208348 (Box 19, Folder 115)
    - Tony, undated; 208349 (Box 19, Folder 116)
    - Toporowicz, Maciek, 1989; 208350 (Box 19, Folder 117)
    - Topp, Mike, 1985; 208351 (Box 19, Folder 118)
    - Torr, Diane (includes materials to MRS), 1979-2003, undated; 208352 (Box 19, Folder 119)
    - Torrey, Ella King, 1992; 208353 (Box 19, Folder 120)
    - Townie and Linda, 1986; 208354 (Box 19, Folder 121)
    - Towns, Edolphus / House of Representatives, 1983; 208355 (Box 19, Folder 122)
    - Townsend, Charlotte, 1973-2000; 208356 (Box 19, Folder 123)
    - Triangle Travel, Inc., 1993; 208357 (Box 19, Folder 124)
    - Trippi, Laura, 1995; 208358 (Box 19, Folder 125)
    - Truck, Fred, 1978; 208359 (Box 19, Folder 126)
    - Trusky, Tom / Hemingway Western Studies Center, 1988-1996; 208360 (Box 19, Folder 127)
    - Tsuda, Rumiko, 1998-2000; Undated; 208361 (Box 19, Folder 128)
    - Tucker, Marcia, 1976-1998; 208362 (Box 19, Folder 129)
    - Turnbaugh, Douglas Blair, 1984; 208363 (Box 19, Folder 130)
    - [Turner], Bob, 1963; 208364 (Box 19, Folder 131)
    - Turturro, John, 1985; 208365 (Box 19, Folder 132)
    - Two Girls Working, 2001-2004; 208366 (Box 19, Folder 133)
    - Tyman, Derek, 1987; 208367 (Box 19, Folder 134)
    - Tyson, James, 2001; 208368 (Box 19, Folder 135)
    - University of Bristol / Nikki Milican, 2007; 208369 (Box 19, Folder 136)
    - University of California, Davis / Barbara Sellers-Young, 2008; 208370 (Box 19, Folder 137)
    - University of Chicago / Laura Latinsky, 2006; 208371 (Box 19, Folder 138)
    - University of Iowa, School of Art and Art History / Wallace J. Tomasini, 1990; 208372 (Box 19, Folder 139)
    - University of Washington Flying Club, Undated; 208373 (Box 19, Folder 140)
    - Unsent Postcards, Undated; 208374 (Box 19, Folder 141)
    - Unsigned Correspondence, Undated; 208375 (Box 19, Folder 142)
    - Unsigned Correspondence, Undated; 208376 (Box 19, Folder 143)
    - Unsigned Correspondence, Undated; 208377 (Box 19, Folder 144)
    - Unsigned Chain Letters, Undated; 208378 (Box 19, Folder 145)
    - Ursone, Adele, 1992; 208379 (Box 19, Folder 146)
    - Ute, 1995; 208380 (Box 19, Folder 147)
    - V. & G. & B., 1980; 208381 (Box 19, Folder 148)
    - V Tape / Mark Pellegrino, 2007; 208382 (Box 19, Folder 149)
    - Vaillancourt DellaPenna, Sandy, 1991; 208383 (Box 19, Folder 150)
    - Valborg and Tim, Undated; 208384 (Box 19, Folder 151)
    - Van Allen, Bonnie, 1988-1998; 208385 (Box 19, Folder 152)
    - Van Dalen, Anton, 1986-2007; Undated; 208386 (Box 19, Folder 153)
    - Van Deckter, Gigi, 1995; 208387 (Box 19, Folder 154)
    - VanderStoop, Wanda / V Tape, 1996; 208388 (Box 19, Folder 155)
    - Van Horn, Erica (contains materials from Martha Wilson), 1995-2008; Undated; 208417 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Van Mechelen, Marga, 2007; 208418 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - [Vaseur], Annie / Aubes 3935, 1986; 208419 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Vasic, Vesna, 2000-2001; 208420 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Vater, Regina, 1984-1989; 208421 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Vaughan, Karen, 2001; 208422 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Vera, Veronica, 1993; 208423 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Vermont College / Dong Ashford, 2000-2001; 208424 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Virginia, 1976; 208425 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Vivell, Judith, Undated; 208426 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Von Zweck, Dina, 2002; Undated; 208427 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - [W], Arnold, 1971; 208428 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Waag, Carol, 1994; 208429 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Wade and Heitner, Randy, Marty and Sage, 1991; 208430 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Wageman, Virginia / Art Journal, 1993; 208431 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Waitzkin, Stella, 1976; 208432 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Walczak, Larry, 1996; 208433 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Wallach, Amei, 2005; Undated; 208434 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Wallie, 1976; 208435 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Walsh, Alexander, 2001; 208436 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Walsh, Alida, 1986-1987; 208437 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Walt, 1967-1969; Undated; 208438 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Walter, 1993; 208439 (Box 20, Folder 23)